mt5traders.com 2019-05-02

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which mt5traders.com collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of the https://www.mt5traders.com website (“Site”).

This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by mt5traders.com.

### Who we are

Our website address is: https://www.mt5traders.com.

### Personal identification information

Mt5traders.com collects personal identification information from its Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us, fill out our website contact form and/or subscribe to our email newsletter.

Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

Mt5traders.com will not retain your personal information longer than is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected or as required by applicable laws or regulations. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously.

### Non-personal identification information

Mt5traders.com collects non-personal identification information about its Users whenever they interact with the site.

Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of information sent by a website to a Visitor’s hard disk. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.

By continuing to visit the website, you agree to the placement of cookies on your device.

If you choose not to accept our cookies, we cannot guarantee that your experience will be as fulfilling as it would otherwise be.

The use of cookies is widespread and benefits the surfer.

### Collection and use of User data

Mt5traders.com collects and uses User data for the following purposes:

– To improve the mt5traders.com site (Non-personal identification information)

– To send our email newsletter (Only email address required*)

*If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### General Data Protection Regulation – GDPR

The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) is a regulation on data protection and privacy for all individuals. To comply with this regulation we adopted (or are able to adopt):

  * We only collect necessary data. For example, your email address when you subscribe to our newsletter.
  * We do not share personal data with 3rd party.
  * You can unsubscribe (remove your email address) at any time at the bottom of each and every email. This action is irreversible.You will need to sign up again.

### Safety of your personal information

Please be assured that we never sell, trade, or rent any of your personally identifiable information to third party websites or companies for any purposes.

### Third party websites

Users may find advertising or content on mt5traders.com that contain links to third party sites. We do not control the content that appear on these third party sites.

In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies.

Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website’s own terms and policies.

### Advertising

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies.

These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer.

This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Changes to this privacy policy

Mt5tradersr.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page.

We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect.

You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site.

Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
